Now I'm ready to treat.
I've prepped Matt.
I've got his hair ready.
We've spoke about what he'd like and what treatment he wants.
He's made the decision of electrology.
So now, we're going to start our work.
I have the timer on and we're working.
Now these hairs are growing downward and there is a kind of, this way that I hold the probe in my hand and I taunt that skin, so I get that hair just at the right angle, and then in we go, and then to see what it takes to do Matt's hair in the back.
This hair is a little bit different.
I need to go a little bit deeper and stay a little bit longer.
There we go.
It's treated perfect.
So now we continue.
Now that I know what it takes, I'm off and running.
There we go.
Another hair another hair, and this is the blend.
So this is a little slower than if it was high frequency.
High frequency would be probably almost half the time to treat as it is the blend.
But it's the numbers on that treatment is somewhere in the forty percentile,fifty percentile,with high frequency vs. up to eighty nine or ninety per cent kill ratio, when you use the blend.
So I like those numbers.
So that's kind of why I go that direction, and I don't like fast and hot and quick.
You have too much imperfection in the work, as far as I'm concerned.